# Enrique Marin

Developer & Designer - B.C.S. MX

enriquemarin.xyz enrique.marin.h@hotmail.com +52 612 104 9341



I am a young developer enthusiastic about innovative and technological projects that seek to impact people's lives. In recent years I have worked in areas such as web development and mobile Apps, as well as graphic creation projects such as branding and digital marketing.

### Skills

#### Languages

HTML&CSS \*
JavaScript \*
Dart \*
C#
SQL
NonSQL

# Tech / Frameworks

Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Node.js, AdonisJS, MongoDB, MySQL, SQL Server, NGinx, Flutter, Firebase, Android Studio, Git, Visual Studio Code

### Design

Illustrator \*
Adobe Xd \*
Photoshop
After Effects

#### Idioms

Spanish (native) English (B2)

## Experience

Applab.mx Sep 2021 – Nov 2021 (3 months)

Front End Web Developer (Remote)

Web developer focused on creating websites for businesses and clients looking for a more customized design. My goal was to complete a series of web projects in a span of 3 months.

Freelance 2020 - 2021

Brand Designer, UI Designer & Web Developer

Independent professional focused on development services of web systems, brand design, interface design (UI / UX).

Async Agencia Creativa 2019 – 2020 (13 months)

CoFounder, Designer & Web Developer

Async is an agency dedicated to inpulse companies and entrepreneurs into the digital world through branding, marketing and websites.

Relapp 2019 (6 months)

Brand Designer, UI Designer & App Developer (Flutter)

App sudcalifornian to search all kind of local business and promos in your town.

Cortêz Baja Sur 2018 - 2019 (6 months)

CoFounder, Illustrator & Brand Designer

Clothing brand with a local urban concept that encourages love for Baja California Sur.

JastMedia 2018 – 2019 (2 months)

Front-End Developer, Content Loader

Juniper Data Center's Extending Department Focused on Websites Development for clients in United States

### Education

**Bachelor in Computing Systems** 2018

Tecnológico Nacional de México Campus La Paz

Security & Web Development speciality



@enriquemarin\_mx







# Enrique Marin

Developer & Designer - B.C.S. MX

enriquemarin.xxyz enrique.marin.h@hotmail.com +52 612 104 9341



Soy un joven desarrollador entusiasta por proyectos innovadores y tecnológicos que busquen impactar la vida de las personas. En los últimos años me he desenvuelto en áreas como desarrollo web y Apps móviles, al igual que proyectos de creación gráfica como branding y marketing digital.

### Skills

### Lenguajes

HTML&CSS \*
JavaScript \*
Dart \*
C#
SQL
NoSQL

# Tech / Frameworks

Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Node.js, AdonisJS, MongoDB, MySQL, SQL Server, NGinx, Flutter, Firebase, Android Studio, Git, Visual Studio Code

#### Diseño

Illustrator \*
Adobe Xd \*
Photoshop
After Effects

#### Idiomas

Español (nativo) Ingles (B2)

## Experiencia

Applab.mx Sep 2021 – Nov 2021 (3 months)

Desarrollador Web Front End (Remoto)

Desarrollador web enfocado en crear sitios web para negocios y clientes que buscan un diseño más personalizado. Mi objetivo fue realizar una serie de proyectos web en un lapso de 3 meses.

Freelance 2020 - 2021

Diseñador de Marca, Diseñador UI y Desarrollador Web

Profesionista independiente enfocado a servicios de desarrollo de sistemas web, diseño de marca, diseño de interfaces (UI / UX).

Async Agencia Creativa 2019 - 2020 (13 meses)

Cofundador, Diseñador y Desarrollador Web

Async es una agencia dedicada a impulsar a empresas y emprendedores dentro del mundo digital a través de branding, marketing y websites.

Relapp 2019 (6 meses)

Diseñador de Marca, Diseñador UI y Desarrollador Móvil

App sudcaliforniana para buscar todo tipo de empresas y promociones de tu localidad.

Cortêz Baja Sur 2018 - 2019 (6 meses)

Cofundador, Ilustrador y Diseñador de Marca

Marca de ropa con un concepto local urbano que fomenta el amor hacia Baja California Sur.

**JastMedia** 2018 – 2019 (6 meses)

Desarrollador Front-End, Content Loader

Departamento que extiende de Juniper Data Center enfocado en el desarrollo de páginas web para clientes en Estados Unidos

### Educación

Ing. Sistemas Computacionales 2018

Tecnológico Nacional de México Campus La Paz

Especialidad en Seguridad y Desarrollo Web



enriquemarin





/enriquemarin